{
  "chapter": 1,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a limitation of traditional computing approach?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Huge initial investment",
        "Hardware-system management responsibility",
        "Partial utilization of resources",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of cloud computing approach?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "It is ubiquitous",
        "Enabled by pay-for-usage model",
        "Responsiveness",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Access to a Cloud environment it costs more money compared to a traditional environment.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "A Cloud environment can be accessed from anywhere in the world as long as the user has access to the Internet.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one of the following is the standard cloud computing pricing model?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Free",
        "Pay-per-usage",
        "Licensing basis",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Cloud computing makes a business more",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Dynamic", "Strong", "Profitable", "Simple"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following is a feature of utility service?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "24/7 availability",
        "Unlimited access",
        "Metering",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "A computing system is composed of three facility layers. This statement is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following is not considered as a layer in computing system?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Application",
        "Server",
        "Infrastructure",
        "Platform"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Computing network facility falls under which layer of computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Application",
        "Platform",
        "Infrastructure",
        "Both b and c"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Is the IT outsourcing model of traditional computing similar to cloud computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Yes",
        "Not at all",
        "To some extent",
        "Depends on the requirement"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main advantage of utility computing compared to traditional computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Less difficulty",
        "Better security",
        "Economical",
        "Availability"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    }
  ]
}
